(The last chance to advance to Round 3)
(Cheorwon, the regenerative clean city)
(And 8 teams have gathered here.)
(Michelin couple, Kim Hee Eun, 2nd place in Round 1, Lim Ki Hak)
(Busan's best, Kwak Dong Hoon, Brand predator, Kim Ho Yoon)
(Seochon crown prince, Lee Jae Hoon, Franchise master, Kim Kwan Hoon)
(Jo Seo Hyung and Shin Ga Young)
The theme of the revival match is...
(A great restaurant always comes back with rice.)
(Cheorwon Odae Rice)
(Grown with the clean water of Hantan River...)
(and in vast plains that are rich with minerals)
(Create a new dish that showcases the value of Odae Rice)
(Today's reserved guests)
(Those who have enjoyed Odae Rice in Cheorwon for many years)
(100 elderly women)
How should we approach this mission?
This is cooking for mom.
What does my mom like?
Serve 100 guests...
a dish that uses rice...
or goes well with rice.
Each team must prepare one plate...
to fill the octagonal dish that will be used for the revival mission.
It's Chinese-style cuisine.
The plates fall into place perfectly.
Each guest will receive 1 10-dollar bill and 10 1-dollar bills.
For a total of 20 dollars,
they'll decide the price of your dish and pay for it.
The guests determine the price of our dish?
Only the two teams with the highest sales...
will advance to the third round without closing their business.
I'm always confident.
I'm feeling lucky today.
Something elderly women would love.
Let's make something familiar yet new.
What's clear is that we'll compete with flavour.
Let's give it everything we've got like it's our last performance.
Each team will receive 200 dollars for ingredients.
- Two hundred dollars?
- You can go to the Grocery Store...
to buy supplies.
- It's ten dollars per person.
- The budget is too small.
The reservation time is 12:30pm.
(5 hours from now)
- We don't have much time.
- There's not a lot of time.
The Arena Grocery Store provides basic seasoning,
equipment, and kitchen tools.
However, the quantity of equipment...
and tools is limited.
It's all about the equipment.
Let's make sure to take the pressure cooker.
- Here's the Arena Grocery Store.
- Please start...
- your strategy meeting now.
- Last time, it was here.
- Shall we write it down?
- Let's get going.
- What?
- We have to go now.
(Jo Seo Hyung is the first one to run over.)
- What is it? Perilla seeds?
- Perilla seeds.
Green plum syrup.
Let's get two packs of glutinous rice.
And one pancake flour.
(Finishing with a bag of rice)
(The Star In My Heart)
(The free shopping is complete.)
As soon as I saw rice,
the first thing I thought was making side dishes.
I tasted the rice as soon as we arrived.
It's good.
The more you chew Odae Rice, the sweeter it gets.
The moist texture created...
by the natural sweetness...
allows the side dishes to draw you in...
and absorb the flavours.
I thought several different side dishes would...
let people experience a wider range of tastes.
Something with perilla seeds like a mustard-based cold salad.
- It'd go well with scallions.
- A cold salad?
Or we could blanch squid...
and mix it with chestnuts.
Let's toss bracken with squid and perilla oil.
I'm good at making side dishes,
so I will definitely win.
(What side dishes will the Korean cuisine specialist create?)
(Become rich, Number One)
Think about it carefully.
(Number One)
Is it the right choice?
- The total amount per person is...
- Twenty.
It's 20 dollars.
That's the maximum amount.
What will make us earn 20 dollars?
(The maximum that they can receive through voting is 20 dollars.)
If they're going to set a price,
it'd be better to create a dish...
that's worth paying a high price.
Among all the food I've eaten in my life,
what was the most expensive dish?
How about jeongabok?
How can I make jeongabok?
It's easy to make.
It's expensive because it uses...
many valuable ingredients.
This is about pricing.
Right? You can't value the dish...
at five dollars while eating this.
Let's make something that people will pay 20 dollars for.
When I thought about what kind of food older ladies would pay...
a high price for,
jeongabok came to my mind.
(Jeongabok)
Some places sell it for over 200 dollars.
On average, it's around 100 dollars. It's also priced...
between 60 and 80 dollars.
A fancy dish...
naturally carries a high value.
That's why I chose jeongabok.
Can you make jeongabok with a budget of 200 dollars?
I was surprised. Jeongabok?
I was impressed. It was very impactful.
- We're leaving in five minutes.
- Okay.
(They must buy ingredients at a nearby grocery store.)
With glutinous rice powder...
(Let's run.)
- I'm going to win first place.
- The Star In My Heart.
(Jo Seo Hyung sets out first to a grocery store.)
- Let's hurry.
- We must hurry.
(Additional ingredients up to 200 dollars can be purchased...)
(at a local grocery store.)
(A nearby local grocery store)
(Arriving at the grocery store at 8am)
(4 hours and 30 minutes before the business starts)
- Let's get meat 1st.
- We're the 1st to arrive.
Why are peeled scallions so cheap?
- What's with the prices?
- What's going on here?
- Two bundles should be enough.
- That will be enough.
- Tomatoes are here.
- They have tomatoes.
Enoki mushrooms are only 59 cents.
- Why don't we add them for texture?
- And with this one...
- Are fatsia shoots 80 dollars?
- Yes.
- It's okay.
- The total is 110 dollars so far.
- Is it 110 dollars so far?
- Yes.
Let's go.
(Other teams start to arrive.)
Korean beef briskets are over here.
Our total is only 68 dollars.
For a 3rd of this size, can I get 1 more piece?
Ginger for 70 cents.
We got 3kg of shrimp and 600g of minced pork.
(Kim Hee Eun arrived a little late.)
We must hurry.
We wanted to give the feeling...
of having enjoyed a proper, satisfying meal...
while also eating healthy.
A type of health food.
Shall we use abalone?
Abalone is good.
I wanted to make tteokgalbi...
with abalone and fatsia shoots.
Go.
- We need a shopping cart.
- A shopping cart. Let's go.
(She started by grabbing a lot of fatsia shoots.)
- Hee Eun.
- Yes?
There's no abalone.
(There's no abalone.)
They bought it all.
We bought it all.
It's our main ingredient.
It's also our main ingredient.
- How much did you buy?
- All of it.
- All of this?
- Yes.
We bought it first.
It's also our main ingredient.
Really?
Sir, is there any abalone?
Yes, there is.
- I'll take all of it.
- All of it.
Did you buy all the abalone?
(1.5kg of abalone, 90 dollars)
He bought it all.
I couldn't hide how upset I was.
That much would be perfect for us.
- That much...
- All of it isn't enough for us.
- It's not enough?
- No.
- It's our main ingredient...
- What are you making?
We're making jeongabok.
Jeongabok?
I can understand.
After all, it's their last chance too.
There are no compromises. I would've done the same anyway.
No matter how disappointed I am,
it's not going to make abalone magically appear.
Let's change the plan and move on.
Honey.
Why don't we make something with fatsia shoots and shrimp?
- Without abalone?
- Completely without it.
Thankfully, in the frozen seafood section,
I saw big and plump shrimp.
We'll do it without abalone this time.
This is fate.
(A team is already at the register.)
We'll include the ones...
- Okay.
- that we definitely need.
We definitely need this.
How much is the total so far?
(Breathing nervously)
It's 173 dollars. Let's get one pack of squid.
Okay, let's take this.
- I'm sorry. It's 22 dollars.
- We apologise.
Is that good?
Please.
Is that good? We're over by 28 cents.
Which one shall we take out?
Can we switch minced pork with something else?
With what?
- Oranges.
- Oranges?
How much is minced pork?
It's 5.4 dollars.
When I imagine the pork flavour,
we'll need a citrus flavour like yuzu.
Or...
Then we have to give up on minced pork.
Minced pork?
(Meanwhile, Kim Kwan Hoon is at the next register.)
What?
Sir, we have 50 dollars left. Please bring that here.
- Please bring that here.
- You have 50 dollars left?
- Could you buy this for us?
- What?
Please buy this for us.
Come on, you're rich. Please help me.
I'm a businessman, so I'll buy this and sell it for a high price.
Then I'll pay for it later. Please.
When you add a spoonful of cheonhyehyang in any dish,
- the taste becomes very fancy.
- Right.
Do you want to split it in half?
Let's split it in half.
Does anyone need cheonhyehyang that adds a refreshing flavour?
It's only 6 dollars. The entire pack is 12.5 dollars.
We can buy it and share it in half.
(No one is interested.)
Excuse me, can I buy only half of it?
Or is it possible to buy them individually?
- Yes, it's two dollars for each.
- Is it possible?
It's two dollars for each? That's great.
We should take these out...
and buy this and that instead.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry for causing trouble.
- I'm sorry.
- Have a good day. Goodbye.
- Thank you.
Once we get there, we'll start by blanching fatsia shoots.
(Until the business starts)
(3 hours and 30 minutes)
(The side dish specialist gets ready.)
Shall we start our business?
I grew up in the mountains of Gangwon Province.
Back home,
we rarely use sesame oil.
Almost everything is prepared with perilla oil.
For the fatsia shoots, I lightly blanched them...
and dressed them with perilla oil, green plum syrup,
and a touch of soy sauce.
(Sesame seeds, soy sauce, green plum syrup, perilla oil)
(Seasoned fatsia shoots with perilla oil)
(Gangwon Province-style)
Most of the other chefs specialise in Western cuisine.
There was no other Korean cuisine chef.
When I saw the guests' age group,
I expected some of them to find the meal too heavy.
I hope that they'll enjoy our tomato kimchi...
whenever the food gets heavy.
We have quite a few with bright acidity.
Older ladies will like it. It's a type of kimchi...
that you don't eat every day.
Like the seasoning for cucumber kimchi,
I added chives and regular kimchi seasoning.
(Also adding a broth made with anchovies and vegetables)
By using Daejeo tomatoes,
I made tomato kimchi.
(Refreshing tomato kimchi to cleanse the palate)
I'm sure they like seafood.
(The side dish specialist's secret touch)
(Cheonhyehyang)
I'm going to make a sauce with cheonhyehyang.
Cheonhyehyang is finely blended...
and combined with a touch of mustard and soy sauce for soup.
I made a piquant and savoury sauce.
(Crunchy pear)
(Blanched webfoot octopus, cheonhyehyang sauce)
It looks beautiful.
(Making it sweet with fragrant cheonhyehyang)
The cheonhyehyang fragrance is very strong.
(Cheonhyehyang webfoot octopus salad)
- This is insane.
- It looks so beautiful.
Ideas kept coming to me.
If you're from Gangwon Province, you can't resist tofu.
(Tofu jeon with zucchini and chilli strip)
For the grilled pork belly,
I added a touch of doenjang...
to reduce the sweetness.
(Grilled doenjang marinated pork)
(Stir-fried perilla seeds and mushrooms)
(Seasoned scallions with anchovies)
I focused on the everyday side dishes...
that I ate often when I lived in Gangwon Province.
How many side dishes do we make in a single day?
I'm not exaggerating.
We make about 500 to 600 portions.
Making a wide variety of side dishes in a short amount of time.
That's where my strength lies.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
- We have 7.
- We have 7?
(7 side dishes made in an instant)
Turning everyday side dish into a dish.
Who created this menu?
Please bring her out.
Bring her out.
Other teams will probably compete with one main dish.
This is what makes us different.
What goes well with rice is side dishes.
A plate this small can't hold everything I want to show.
- Over here?
- Yes.
- Right there.
- On top?
(100 servings of 7 side dishes...)
(created by the hands and flavours of Gangwon Province)
(Are you exhausted?)
I'm very tired.
Should we blend strawberries and make something refreshing?
I used this blender earlier for the sauce.
It makes everything very smooth.
For the blueberries, I'll leave a little texture.
(Adding whole frozen strawberries)
"Smoothie."
(Set it to smoothie mode and press start.)
It's surprisingly quiet and blends so smoothly.
There's no need to strain it. It's very fine.
- It's like slush.
- Yes.
- Didn't it turn out so soft?
- It's like slush.
- Exactly.
It's nice and refreshing.
Okay.
What's important is getting the groceries fast.
The moment I saw the rice,
that dish was the first thing that came to mind.
Rice...
We have to make twenty plates.
Without relying on strong artificial seasoning,
I kept thinking about...
what would taste good with rice.
Like yuxiang shiitake mushrooms.
I don't mean the sauce, but the mushrooms.
- Yes.
- For the elders.
It's stylish and tasty.
Talk softly.
Yuxiang, which means fish fragrance, doesn't mean the dish uses fish.
It refers to the dishes which use spicy, sweet, and sour sauce...
that was initially used to cook fish with.
Cheorwon is known for its shiitake mushrooms too.
Fresh shiitake mushrooms...
- They should have them, right?
- I think so.
That's why we need to hurry.
- We must find shiitake mushrooms.
- Shiitake mushrooms first.
If we can't find shiitake mushrooms,
that changes things.
Shiitake...
(Exclaiming)
Here they are.
(Shiitake mushrooms, 1.98 dollars)
It's one of the most impactful shiitake mushrooms...
I've seen in my life.
I'm not lying.
I could smell them from 1m to 2m away.
These mushrooms are insane.
If we get 90, that's around 89 dollars.
Let's check the price.
(Shiitake mushrooms)
We calculated meticulously.
(After a thorough calculation)
- Let's go.
- Okay.
We might not have enough time to prepare.
- I won't be complacent.
- Right. It'll be really hectic.
- I'm desperate.
- Me too.
For me, the memories...
of the 2nd half of Round 2 remain as a big shock to me.
(Can you make more?)
(During the second half, he hurriedly cooked more hot pot.)
I've been cooking for a very long time,
and I prided myself in cooking for the customers.
(With the food burned, they had to make multiple refunds.)
I beat myself up for not being attentive...
until the end.
(I'm so ashamed.)
Regardless of the result,
I should do this well until the end...
so it'll help me improve with my cooking in the future.
I'll do well.
- I'm reflecting on myself.
- Right.
This could become our last round.
I'll stir-fry the vegetables with the sauce by 12pm.
We'll prepare everything in advance...
so we can have it easy.
This time, we'll only serve perfect food.
I'll remove the stems.
Okay.
I can smell shiitake from all the way here.
Fresh shiitake mushrooms smell amazing,
and I want the customers to taste it fully.
The mushrooms look delicious as is.
They just can't taste bad.
Shall we score the mushrooms first?
- I'll do it. You should mince it.
- Okay.
You add shrimp paste into shiitake mushrooms and deep-fry it.
One with coarsely-chopped shrimps...
and the other with finely-minced shrimps.
We prepared two different textures.
For additional texture,
we used burdock...
and shiitake mushrooms.
Ginger and green onions will add to the flavour.
I mixed them all as if kneading.
(The shrimp paste enhances both the flavour and the texture.)
- Let's shape one together.
- Together? Okay.
Put it in.
Make sure you don't trap any air.
Okay.
- Press it down flat.
- Press it?
- Is this too much?
- It's fine.
It will soak in anyway.
Okay.
How long does it take to steam them?
Seven minutes.
We steamed them first.
We cut down on the deep-frying time...
to keep the taste light.
Let's think about how we can make it visually attractive.
I thought of one.
We can't make the batter in advance.
- It'll be real-time.
- Yes.
It'll be less crispy because it's not fermented enough.
It'll be good to deep-fry rice,
blend it, and add it to the batter.
(The frying batter mixed with deep-fried ground rice)
To add the crispy texture,
I thought about adding rice to the batter.
I'll deep-fry just this much rice.
Okay.
Deep-fried rice would taste savoury.
I'll add that flavour to the batter, no matter how little it may be,
so that the overall taste connects to the flavour of rice naturally.
(He enhances the flavour by deep-frying rice.)
(He blends it finely to turn it into ground rice.)
Ground rice.
It's not steamed rice with a random dish.
It's steamed rice with rice-flavoured dish.
So the flavour connects naturally.
(Deep-fry steamed mushrooms to complete it.)
As crispy as possible.
While retaining the mushroom flavour.
It's done. You can taste it now.
Will your mom be moved when she eats this?
Yes.
The shrimp flavour and the texture are nice.
(Deep-fried mushrooms have turned out to be crispy.)
The juiciness of shrimps...
and the chewiness and softness of shiitake mushrooms.
(Yuxiang sauce whets your appetite.)
Sweet, sour, and spicy yuxiang sauce.
I thought they would harmonize nicely.
This must have a strong impact.
I just hoped that the customers would think the same.
(Yuxiang shiitake mushrooms using Odae Rice batter)
I'll move the hearts of the customers...
and survive the revival match.
Good luck to us.
The neighbour seniors.
- I didn't expect them to be women.
- Me neither.
Do they farm rice?
It could be fun. Like,
"They created such different texture using our rice."
Since we're using rice,
let's give it the Provence vibe.
I see.
(Cooking a French cuisine for the revival match as well)
When I saw the rice,
I thought of Provence right away.
(Paris, Provence)
That's where rice is harvested.
The red rice...
called Camargue is popular in Provence.
Of course, the rice we're using...
has a very different texture to the rice from Provence.
(Korean rice is smooth and sticky. European rice is less sticky.)
Even though I am using Korean rice,
I wanted the texture to come off completely different,
as if I am using a totally different kind of rice.
So the name of the dish is...
Healthy Provence-style Vegetables Pot Rice.
French cuisine wouldn't work on them.
Who knows?
They could be elegant elderly ladies.
Elegant or not, would this suit their taste?
Hoon, did you start cooking the rice?
I'm going to start now.
(Raw rice)
(The raw rice enters the oven.)
(While the raw rice is roasted...)
- I'll boil the water for the broth.
- Okay.
(Vegetables stock to cook the rice with)
The rice should be roasted by now.
(Checking on the rice which was left in the oven)
(Golden brown)
With the rice we know,
we can't make the fluffy texture.
(The roasted rice goes straight into the rice cooker.)
I added vegetables like onions, green onions,
kabocha squash, and mushrooms after stir-frying them in olive oil.
Can I add Korean wild chives too?
Just add them. We have some left.
Okay.
The fragrance of Korean wild chives...
will play a role as important as...
adding other herbs.
(Roasted rice, various vegetables, and vegetable stock)
The kelp became soft under the sunlight.
I'm behind you. Rice incoming.
(Put it into the rice cooker, and the pot rice is ready.)
I chose pork shoulder.
I'll confit pork shoulder in oil.
(Confit: A French cooking method of putting ingredients into oil...)
(and cooking it slowly in low heat)
(You must check the temperature frequently.)
The fire didn't extinguish, did it?
- Now...
- Can you see it?
- I think it's turned off.
- Right?
There you go.
(Blaze up)
The flame kept going out.
You need to maintain a very low heat.
When I reduced the heat a tad bit, the wind kept blowing out the fire.
(Adding kindlings)
(Failed)
I can't see it.
That was a challenge.
(Oven)
(He removes the oven tray.)
My gosh.
I compared the size of the pot with the oven next to it,
and it looked like the pot would fit.
So I put the whole thing into the oven.
(The pot fits into the oven nicely.)
Be careful when you take it out.
As a result, I could cook it more stably.
Done.
(Lim Ki Hak's improvisation)
(While the meat is getting cooked in the oven, )
(he completes the ratatouille that will be put onto the rice.)
(Opening the rice cooker)
It's cooked well.
It's fluffy.
(Like the French rice, the rice is fluffy.)
It's delicious.
- Is it all cooked?
- Yes.
"It's not the rice we know."
Wouldn't that be a fun experience if they say like that?
I agree.
That'd be a success.
It should be thick like porridge.
They're elderly.
I know, but...
It's salty for seniors.
I'm planning to make a risotto which the seniors can enjoy too.
Something which isn't too greasy or heavy.
Since it's spring,
we wanted to make a fresh risotto...
with seafood.
We really need to showcase our pasta.
We'll show them our pasta in the next mission.
We cook Italian cuisine,
and our restaurant is well-known for our pasta.
But we had to cook using rice for this mission,
so we boldly excluded pasta.
I really want to survive and showcase our pasta...
in the next mission.
I can't get eliminated like this.
Please allow me to continue to participate.
(The perfect restaurant name for the mission)
We'll definitely make it.
(The young owners are spirited.)
With the resolve to cook the dishes as delicious as the grandma's,
we came up with the name.
- They're very elderly.
- Oh, no.
- What should we do?
- This...
- In their 60s and 70s?
- We're doomed.
Hey.
A military unit is better.
- This is bad.
- A military unit is better. This...
There's a high chance we're going to a military unit.
(The couple was very sure they were going to a military unit.)
Soldiers nowadays are young,
so they'd like western cuisine too.
They'll like tasty, strong-flavoured food.
We can't go with the sauce I thought of.
It's too greasy and strong.
After discovering the age range,
we changed everything.
We were thinking about a strong and straightforward flavour.
But after seeing that their ages ranged from 60s to 70s...
(Strong flavour out)
(Greasiness out)
We were going to throw in tons of meat and seafood.
But I don't think that's suitable.
We scrapped everything we planned.
Let's rack our brains quickly.
This is bad.
Let's discuss.
It's very different from what we expected.
It's so hard to cook for seniors.
(Don't Tell Grandma's quest to captivate the seniors' taste buds)
Goodness.
I'm only good at making broth.
All of our dishes...
require a lot of broth.
Mild and light flavour.
(Customization 1. Make it light with seafood broth.)
I added crabs, seashells, and mussels,
and kept boiling it.
We cook broth yet again today.
Season it lightly, and don't add too much butter and cheese.
Okay.
Always milder than what you usually prefer.
- Okay.
- Two levels lower.
(Customization 2. Make sure it's less salty!)
The teams which cook strong-flavoured food will lose.
It does smell good.
But just a bit. The seasoning...
(Finding the best seasoning by tasting it nonstop)
Isn't it too bland?
- No.
- No?
- Okay, I'll stop here.
- Yes, let's go.
Okay.
Nice.
Actually, people have it as al dente in Italy.
But for the seniors, we'll cook it a lot longer.
(Customization 3. Cook the rice for long so it's easy to eat.)
It tastes fresh,
so I was sure they'd like it.
And it has 4 types of seafood, not just 1.
The seafood we used...
are abalones, webfoot octopus, and shrimps.
(Abalones, flounder, webfoot octopus, shrimps)
Fatsia shoots taste really good when grilled in oil.
I placed grilled fatsia shoots on the risotto.
(Flounder, fatsia shoots, abalone, webfoot octopus, shrimp)
Just one dish will decide the winners.
We must pour our everything into it.
We're second to none when it comes to the taste,
but that doesn't secure our victory.
We're almost done.
- I'm sure they'll enjoy this.
- I'll put one there.
As long as they're served as we've prepared,
they would like it. Right?
(Spring Vegetables Risotto by Don't Tell Grandma is ready.)
Do I need to make the side dishes using rice?
(Everything About Tteokbokki)
(And this man here is full of concerns.)
I only know how to make tteokbokki,
and I'm only good at making tteokbokki.
(A great restaurant always comes back with rice.)
(When the mission was revealed)
What's this?
Are we only using rice?
Since you make tteokbokki, will you make your own rice cake?
How can I make it using that?
Rice?
The dishes I can cook...
are street food and tteokbokki.
(He did not expect the mission.)
Here...
(Mumbling)
A dish that goes well with rice...
or a dish using rice.
(A dish that goes well with rice or a dish using rice?)
Something healthy...
- and soft.
- Yes, for sure.
I came up with this. Since we're in Gangwon Province,
we can make rice dough balls and perilla seed cream.
- Perilla seed cream.
- Yes, perilla seed cream.
It's super delicious. It's totally...
- Rice dough balls...
- The seniors...
- will like it too.
- Yes. A warm dish.
Perilla seed rice dough balls with thick soup.
I'm from Gangwon Province.
People in Gangwon Province...
enjoy eating perilla seed potato ball soup.
(Potato ball: Local food of Gangwon Province)
(Ground potatoes are made into balls.)
I'll use the Cheorwon rice to make rice dough balls...
and make tteokbokki with them, using not just perilla seed...
but cream too.
It will taste exotic...
and local at the same time.
You should be able to taste various flavours.
That's what I decided on.
(But...)
How do we make rice cake?
(How on earth will he make rice dough balls?)
There was no machine to make rice cakes.
I didn't have a mallet...
nor a mortar.
How will we make rice cakes out of plain rice?
I'm having a rush of dopamine.
This is fun.
Should I chop down a tree and make a mallet?
A tree...
Someone else's tree.
And a thought flashed in my mind.
I saw something just now.
(Looking around)
Here it is.
(What caught Kwan Hoon's eyes...)
Okay.
There was a rolling pin, which was also made of trees.
You're supposed to use it to roll dough, actually.
I choose you.
(It will be his mallet for the day.)
I was only thinking about how I could make rice cakes.
I just went "whatever" and took it with me.
Nice.
Let's go now.
(Freshly-steamed Cheorwon Odae Rice)
There are so many things to do.
For the first time in my life, I used a blender to blend rice.
I blended it until 30 percent of the rice maintained its form.
That's because...
rice dough ball feels very chewy...
when it still has the bit of texture to it.
(The 1st round of chewy rice dough is completed.)
And to add the stickiness,
I added potato starch, the amount being 20 percent...
of the total amount of rice.
I prepared the dough as if I was making potato balls.
(20 percent potato starch, 80 percent rice)
(100 percent handmade rice dough balls)
(The dough starts getting stickier.)
Okay, we can do it.
(Very serious)
I can do it.
Good.
The bat is a bit small.
If air pockets form inside the rice cake...
and you boil it or steam it,
the inside becomes hollow like bread.
When that happens,
the chewy texture disappears.
You're making more work for yourself.
You should either beat it good with a mallet...
or press it down using a machine to push out the air.
It's called compressibility.
(Compressing)
Darn it.
I might break the worktable.
It was an impossible situation, but I tried to make rice cake.
It's insane, but as I did it...
Look at how sticky it is.
The more I hit, the more glutinous it gets.
When I felt that it was turning into rice cake in a way,
I felt a burst of dopamine and thrill.
I enjoyed the sense of accomplishment.
I watched him from the side,
and he looked like...
a woman beating her laundry with a laundry bat by the stream.
(Oiling the tray)
(Now that he's made the rice cake dough, )
(it's time to shape it.)
(Rolling it into balls)
(Made rice dough ball)
Little did I think I'd make rice-based tteok on the spot.
I know, right?
Tteokbokki exists everywhere.
The texture feels a lot like glutinous mochi.
The colour is spot on.
It's white as snow.
(Everything About Tteokbokki)
My flattery skills are going to improve.
But I have no one to flatter now.
(CEO of a 270 million dollar annual revenue company)
(Rolled out about 300 rice dough balls)
It's hot.
Done. The balls are floating.
(Scooping out the floating rice balls with a strainer)
(Rinsing them in cold water)
(Rice dough balls are done!)
Okay.
As for the sauce, I'm cooking onions...
and garlic in butter for the aroma first.
Into that mix, fresh cream and milk are added in a 2-to-1 ratio.
Button mushrooms are thrown into the pot for that mushroom aroma.
There's one key ingredient.
Two pieces of peperoncino.
I wanted the customers to feel, "Wait! A clean aftertaste?"
That was why I only added two pieces of peperoncino.
Lastly, I mixed in a generous amount of perilla seed powder.
(Adding in the rice dough balls and perilla seed powder last)
It's so that the customers can taste...
the aroma of Gangwon Province's perilla seeds.
(Perilla seed cream rice dough ball)
All set.
It is currently 12:24pm.
The guests with reservations are entering.
I can smell something good.
The smell of meat. I'm hungry.
My guess is that they cook in there and bring out the food.
Extraordinary Couple.
Everything About Tteokbokki. Number One.
Here they are.
They are as old as my mom.
One minute?
Okay, we can serve it now.
All of them are set.
I can smell meat.
- There are five people...
- All reserved guests have entered.
(All 100 reserved guests are seated.)
My stomach is growling hard because of the smell of food.
Perilla seed cream sauce. Made with rice from Cheorwon.
(Menu with the names and descriptions of the dishes)
Try to evaluate which dish was the best.
Teams, please serve the dish to each table.
- Hi.
Thank you.
- Rice dough ball...
- Yes?
Made with rice from Cheorwon, Gangwon Province.
It's a perilla seed rice dough ball.
- Thank you.
- Perilla rice dough ball cream.
Enjoy.
- It looks good.
- These are fatsia shoots...
and squash.
- Eat them while they're crispy.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Hi.
We prepared seven side dishes...
you can enjoy with rice.
Here are tomato kimchi,
stir-fried perilla seed mushroom namul,
and salad with cheonhyehyang and webfoot octopus.
Crown daisy and pear are at the bottom.
Have them together.
Tofu was grilled in perilla oil.
You can have it...
- with fatsia shoots.
- Enjoy.
Rice dough balls. I'm from...
- Gangwon Province.
- Have them together, okay?
- Perilla seed cream.
- Enjoy.
You know it's Gangwon Province's famous ingredient.
I'm also from Gangwon Province.
- Enjoy.
- We will.
- Hi, ma'am.
- Hi.
Let me serve you our dish.
The dish we prepared today is what's called...
jeongabok.
The real dish that wishes for health and prosperity.
(A masterpiece with the delicacies from land and sea)
There's a saying that you'll get rich if you eat this.
- Please try it and become rich.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Thank you.
- The food is good.
- I'm glad.
- It's good.
- Please remember jeongabok.
- Jeongabok.
You don't have to remember the others.
We made a delicious risotto...
out of Cheorwon Odae Rice.
On top is tteokgalbi made with...
Korean beef and Korean pork cooked over charcoal.
- What is it?
- Is it risotto?
Yes, we made it less thick, like porridge.
The hand warmer is to keep the dish warm for you.
What was always disappointing was that...
we were unable to serve the hot dishes warm.
So we used up...
all the hand warmers we had.
The broth is based on dried seaweed and doenjang.
- Hi.
- What is that?
We're serving French cuisine.
Odae Rice was toasted raw...
to make it light and fluffy.
The sauce was made with doenjang.
It's best when you mix it with rice.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- Go ahead.
Here's risotto made with fresh spring vegetables and wild greens,
served with four kinds of seafood.
Excuse me, ma'am.
This is Sichuan-style yuxiang sauce.
The dish is yuxiang shiitake mushrooms,
featuring fresh shiitake mushrooms...
stuffed with minced burdock root and shrimp.
Enjoy it with rice while it's warm.
It's stuffed with ingredients.
(Shin Ga Young, Lim Ki Hak, Kim Hee Eun, Jo Seo Hyung, )
(Kim Kwan Hoon, Kim Ho Yoon, Kwak Dong Hoon, Lee Jae Hoon)
(The chefs can watch it live from the monitor room.)
Customers around that age...
would have a traditional palate.
I wonder how they think about our dish.
I'm sure at least half of the dishes...
are new to them.
Right?
Old ladies are accurate when it comes to evaluating.
(What did the old ladies think about the dishes?)
- It's made with Odae Rice.
- Correct.
Everything was cooked with Odae Rice.
Let's try the rice dough ball.
(Perilla seed cream rice dough ball from Everything About Tteokbokki)
It's mine.
It's really good.
It really is.
- Which one?
- The rice dough ball.
The sauce.
I'm thinking...
the rice dough ball was made with steamed rice.
I can feel the rice grains.
Use your tongue. You can feel the rice grains.
It's made with Odae Rice.
- You can feel the rice, right?
- Yes.
It's a dish made with rice.
I was hoping the customers would focus on...
how Cheorwon rice was used.
Remember, I asked if you weren't making rice cakes?
It almost killed me.
I heard things break next door.
No wonder our kitchen shook and all.
- It was me.
- I see.
- Give me one of each.
- Is it dried seaweed?
- Dried seaweed?
- One each, please.
Push it in.
Give me a second.
Fatsia shoot fritter is good.
- What's good?
- Fatsia shoot fritter.
(Crunchy)
The fatsia shoots are super crunchy.
It's crunchy.
(And next to the rice dough balls)
Fatsia shoots and squash.
(Fatsia shoots and kabocha squash fritters)
Fatsia shoots.
This ingredient could be the highlight.
- Fatsia shoots.
- Fatsia shoots. These are big ones.
(Fatsia shoots)
It was deep-fried to keep the aroma.
(Fatsia shoot fritters with the scent of spring)
It smells much stronger.
The fatsia shoots are great.
Give me some fatsia shoots. I want to deep-fry some.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
What a relief.
What's this?
It's risotto and seafood.
(Spring Vegetables Risotto by Shin Ga Young)
It's ours.
Risotto is much like porridge, so I'm sure they'll enjoy it.
This one is good too.
This one is delicious. It is.
- It's not mustard, so what is it?
- It's not mustard.
Is it beans?
(Spring vegetables salsa verde: Sauce made from extracted juices)
Here. Try it.
I like how it's not salty.
Is it delicious?
The finishing touches were...
It's too salty.
- Salty?
- Yes.
We try to make it bland,
but the elders always ask us to make it more bland.
You're right. We should make it bland.
It's this one. The aromatic spring vegetables.
Risotto and seafood.
That's risotto and seafood.
It felt like they recognised that effort.
Didn't we have many risotto dishes?
It looked like we had several.
- This is another risotto.
- Yes.
All the rice dishes are risotto.
(Kim Hee Eun made a different kind of risotto.)
- The dish was no joke.
- I know, right?
- With a grand topping.
- What was no joke about it?
It's just tteokgalbi.
- No, it wasn't just tteokgalbi.
- No.
(Shrimp, shiitake mushroom, fatsia shoots)
I think one of the customers just scooped some of our risotto.
This is like porridge, isn't it?
I told them it was Italian-style porridge,
in case they didn't know risotto.
- Risotto? It's risotto.
- Yes.
It's something a lot like tteokgalbi.
She said it was tteokgalbi.
- It's good.
- Hold on.
Is it good?
- It's very soft.
- It's good.
I'm a fan of this one.
- Which one?
- The risotto.
(Kim Hee Eun's risotto gets good reviews.)
The one with tteokgalbi?
I heard it was something with porridge and dried seaweed.
Imagine how happy the old ladies must be to be served food...
after cooking for others every single day.
Eating food made by someone else is...
- amazing.
- Totally.
Little did I think such a day would come.
(Laughing)
Really.
Tell them to host this every year.
Every year, okay?
- It's all rice, right?
- Yes.
This one is...
Provence-style vegetable pot rice.
It's totally different from risotto, right?
- The texture of the rice.
- It's the complete opposite.
I wonder if the customers will like the texture.
What if they say, "It's not thoroughly cooked?"
But it seemed like the rice was fully cooked.
- It's like something we always had.
- We're used to it.
This one tastes much like pizza.
- Pizza.
- I like it.
- It's French.
- Something like that.
Like Korean steamed rice.
- I'm full.
- I prefer mushy rice.
(The lady next to her also tries a spoonful.)
- So?
- You've got to chew for a while.
(Shaking her head)
(The lady next to her also tries a spoonful.)
- So?
- You've got to chew for a while.
(Shaking her head)
The rice in this one is... You know...
- It's not sticky rice.
- The rice is fluffy.
It reminds me of fried rice.
This Odae Rice tastes like a different type of rice.
- How come?
- It's like Vietnamese rice.
- It was roasted. That's why.
- The rice was roasted.
The rice is all fluffy and nice.
(Did the old ladies like the French-style pot rice?)
Trying something new is really enjoyable.
Totally.
- We're having luxurious food today.
- Really.
- Where else would we have this?
- Exactly.
What was this one again?
Jeongabok.
- It has abalone inside.
- Right.
- It's a high-end dish.
- Let's try it.
When will we ever get to eat something like this?
It'd cost a fortune...
- Think of the price.
- if we had it at a hotel.
Have an abalone each.
Abalone is a pricey dish.
Who used abalone?
Over here. Jeongabok.
- Jeongabok.
- Three delicacies.
It's an expensive dish.
I don't think they'll write down five dollars for it.
I was hoping my dish would look expensive.
If the old ladies were to put a price on each dish,
I thought it'd be best to make a dish...
that would command a higher price.
- Jeongabok is a great idea.
- For real.
If you made a dish look more pricey with the same money for ingredients,
- that's a skill of yours.
- Totally.
This one's amazing.
(Yuxiang shiitake mushrooms by Kim Ho Yoon)
How's this one?
She asked how it was.
- It's good.
- I'm savouring it right now.
- Try it.
- Okay.
(Yuxiang shiitake mushrooms by Kim Ho Yoon)
It's rice inside.
The mushroom was grilled until golden...
- with rice inside.
- There's shrimp inside.
Yes, there's seafood.
- Seafood. Shrimp.
- The mushroom is the best part.
The rice has been grilled until golden at the end.
- This one?
- Yes.
- The outside?
- Like nurungji.
- Yes.
- Try it.
How did they stuff the filling?
Right? Cooking it... Gosh.
What's the name of this dish again? It's good.
- Raw shiitake mushroom...
- Shrimp paste.
- shrimp paste.
- Shrimp paste?
- I like that one better.
- Me too.
This shiitake mushroom is great.
Is it?
- Yes.
- It's good.
I wonder how it will turn out.
The reaction...
Every dish will get a full score.
All of them are good.
It's good. Try the shiitake mushroom. There's only one left.
Have it.
(Glancing)
- What did you cook?
- Seven side dishes.
- Seven?
- Amazing.
It's all or nothing.
The others made main dishes.
(The only side dish)
As I had expected, there were many risottos.
I thought the customers would need something refreshing at one point.
The outside?
- My stomach feels unsettled.
- Suddenly?
Everything is...
a bit cheesy.
It was good at first.
- I want kimchi.
- Same here.
There aren't many refreshing dishes.
All were heavy.
We should've added some Cheongyang chilli pepper.
These must be side dishes for rice.
She said they were side dishes.
The side dishes look good with the rice.
Totally.
It's called Spring Picnic Feast.
(Spring Picnic Feast by Jo Seo Hyung)
It's good.
The tomato kimchi is great.
Try the tomato kimchi.
The tomato kimchi is the best.
The cheonhyehyang inside...
Right? It takes away...
that oiliness.
Yes, the tanginess...
- This one?
- balances out the richness.
I like the side dishes.
If they considered the side dishes as one cuisine,
we might have a chance of surviving.
If we were to rank them 1st, 2nd, and 3rd...
Among these?
This comes in first place for me.
- Oh, my. Really?
- All were good, no?
I choose this one.
- This was the best.
- First place.
I can't decide as everything was just too good.
True. I'm wavering.
At first...
I was happy to see them enjoying the dishes.
But when the time to evaluate came,
they all turned...
cool-headed and sharp.
I put my soul into it.
I want to advance.
What if we have to close our store soon?
If it's 2 teams out of the 8 teams...
Thanks to them, I had a delicious meal.
(The 100 guests are done dining.)
- Voting.
- We have to vote.
We have to leave after voting in that booth.
- What about this one?
- I'm going with this one.
(Voting with 1 10-dollar bill and 10 1-dollar bills)
This one.
That was good too.
(They can use 20 dollars for 1 dish or multiple dishes.)
Do I put it in here?
- I choose this one.
- This dish was the best.
I enjoyed this one.
All done.
(The 100 guests are done voting.)
The revival match has ended.
I'm getting nervous again.
(Street Arena)
Really, this is cruel.
Luck must be on our side.
Is your fortune good this year?
I don't think so based on how well we're doing.
The jeongabok was...
Is that so?
Should we have just made tteokgalbi and no risotto?
I'm getting flashbacks of how hard spicy stir-fried pork was.
The cauldron soft tofu.
This is stressing me out.
The results...
of the revival match will be announced.
Out of the eight teams,
only the two with the highest revenue...
will revive and advance to Round Three.
(Become rich, Number One)
The possibility...
wasn't dead low.
Won't I make it...
in the top two?
I was fully confident about our dish.
We won't lose. We won't be overpowered. That was all I thought.
We're on the brink.
We must survive.
Here is...
the lowest revenue of the revival match.
- I don't want to hear it.
- This is cruel.
Right?
Are we starting from the bottom?
I'm nervous.
Unbelievable.
Our revenue might be the lowest.
Our dish was creamy.
The final revenue of the eighth place.
One hundred and thirty-two dollars.
What?
- That's mean.
- Among 100 guests?
Yes.
If I were given 10-dollar and 1-dollar bills,
that 10-dollar bill would be my 1st choice.
If I don't get that ten-dollar bill,
it'd be meaningless regardless of how well I do it.
- Right away?
- Please.
Please let us survive.
(Number One, Everything About Tteokbokki, )
(The Star In My Heart, Bol A Bol, Don't Tell Grandma, )
(Extraordinary Couple, Wolfie's, Essence And Technique)
(The Star In My Heart)
The Star In My Heart...
had the lowest revenue and failed to revive.
- What?
The Star In My Heart.
My goodness.
- I thought it was us.
The Star In My Heart.
- It sounded like "Extraordinary."
- I thought it was us.
I guess that was because they served side dishes.
They did a lot of things.
I know.
Was ours worth only 132 dollars?
I don't think it was that bad.
It couldn't beat the main dishes.
The side dishes are not so popular.
These ones?
We have so many fancy dishes here.
It tastes good, though.
We're busy eating other dishes. Since these are side dishes,
we're not eating them yet.
Actually, when I saw...
the ladies holding one-dollar bills,
I realised we picked the wrong menu item.
Side dishes are what people never want to spend a lot of money on.
Because we're used...
to side dishes served for free at a restaurant,
people don't view them as proper dishes on their own.
I completely failed to read their minds.
You never know how things will turn out.
The final revenue of the seventh place...
is 163 dollars.
It's really low.
Bol A Bol has failed to survive.
(7th place: Lim Ki Hak and Kim Hoon)
To be honest, the sales numbers...
are a bit disappointing.
This Odae Rice tastes like a different type of rice.
- How come?
- It's like Vietnamese rice.
The rice is a little...
It has a Western flavour to it.
(They found the French-style pot rice too unfamiliar.)
The rice grains are too light and dry.
The final revenue of the sixth place...
is 175 dollars.
It's so tight.
The gap is less than ten dollars.
- There's barely any difference.
- You're right.
Number One...
has failed to survive.
(6th place: Kwak Dong Hoon and Song Ji Beom)
It’s too salty, so I don't like it.
What's too salty?
Only this one is too salty.
It's a bit on the salty side.
The seasoning styles of Busan and Gangwon Province...
are totally different.
Ours was seasoned the Busan way.
The final revenue of the fifth place...
is 184 dollars.
Wolfie's...
has failed to survive.
(5th place: Lee Jae Hoon and Kim Jin Gyo)
The scores are so close, and they're being so strict.
I bet one team is totally dominating.
(The sales status of the revival match)
(Only the 1st and 2nd places will survive.)
My gosh, this is...
Then, it's us and...
Them and Essence And Technique.
The remaining restaurants are...
Essence And Technique, Extraordinary Couple,
Don't Tell Grandma,
and Everything About Tteokbokki.
- Please.
- Out of these four,
we will now reveal the two restaurants to survive.
- Please.
- Please. Just this once...
(A hearty meal with Korean beef tteokgalbi)
We wanted to give the feeling...
of having enjoyed a proper, satisfying meal...
while also eating healthy.
- Hong Geun.
- Yes?
We can do this.
We used spring vegetables and greens...
to make it fresh and light,
so we were sure they'd love it.
This makes me hold out hope.
Gosh, no. This is too hard.
I was hoping the customers would focus on...
how Cheorwon rice was used.
(Perilla seed cream rice dough ball and fritters)
It’s light but packed with aroma...
and flavour.
(Yuxiang shiitake mushrooms with Odae rice)
The two restaurants that will be revived are...
Please.
- Essence And Technique.
- It's Essence And Technique.
- Everything About Tteokbokki.
- What?
They have been revived.
(Kim Ho Yoon and Jung Chan Hee have survived.)
I didn't see this coming.
- Congratulations.
- What?
(Kim Kwan Hoon and Shin Jong Hun have survived.)
- Congratulations.
- Second place,
Everything About Tteokbokki.
- Good job.
- The final revenue is 377 dollars.
The first place, Essence And Technique.
The final revenue is 529 dollars.
The two restaurants have survived in the revival match.
Great job.
Don't cry.
Why are you crying?
I thought about the customers from the 2nd half of Round 2.
"Let's do it right this time."
"Let's make it even more delicious for them."
Taste this one more time.
What if we make it a bit sweeter?
It's a little spicy.
We need to tone it down and make it smoother.
The sesame oil aroma isn't really coming through.
I wanted to stay completely focused...
and make sure the same mistake will never happen again.
All I could think was to make the food taste better.
I like the mushroom dish the best.
I'll grab another shiitake mushroom.
The shiitake mushroom is great.
You guys like the mushroom dish, right?
I think the mushroom dish will take first place.
- Okay.
- This was definitely the best.
(132 dollars, 163 dollars, 175 dollars, 184 dollars)
The mushroom.
It was great.
- I liked this one best.
- Only this one.
We took up a quarter of the total budget,
so mathematically speaking, that's a very high rate.
We learn so much from every single round.
I'm so happy that I'm given one more chance like this.
I think we should change our name to Everything About Drama.
Everything we do is quite dramatic.
(Round 1)
Everything About Tteokbokki. Congratulations.
(They survived in 18th place out of 20 teams.)
(They fought neck and neck against Lee Yeon Bok, the master chef.)
(But they suffered a heartbreaking defeat.)
We always dropped to rock bottom,
but we grabbed a lifeline to climb back up again and again.
That’s what happened this time too.
For me, the rice dough ball is number one.
- The rice dough ball.
- I like it.
- It's nice.
- I like the cream sauce.
I'm so grateful to the ladies who enjoyed our dish.
When I looked at their plates, there were no leftovers.
It made the joy of victory twice as sweet.
The six eliminated restaurants...
will leave the Street Arena.
I've been running restaurants for 12 years now,
but I don't think I've ever told myself...
things like, "Good job. You worked hard."
So today, before I leave,
I want to say it to myself just this once.
Good job. You worked hard too.
- Good job.
Running a business is a truly lonely fight.
I've been through so much over those 12 years.
Even though I got eliminated, I want to tell myself...
that I did well.
I believe that my business is the driving force...
that changed my life.
Good restaurants with delicious food always make a comeback.
If someone gets revived,
that means someone else has to pack their bags and go home.
It might have been a little unconventional,
but I hope people will discover the joy...
of experiencing new flavours.
I will take my leave with that in mind.
The biggest problem with this is that...
everyone is doing so much better than I expected.
I learned a lot from them. I really did.
Everyone says running a business is really hard.
I need to gain more experience and keep building up,
without getting complacent.
I suddenly heard the sound of the shutter...
coming down behind me with a loud noise.
I showed everything I wanted to show.
I feel like I can go home with a light and happy heart.
Hearing people say things like I'm desperately struggling...
or trying way too hard...
actually hurt my feelings at times.
But I realised one thing while doing this.
Isn't desperately struggling better than wasting my life away?
I want to do even better.
Running a business is way too hard.
I feel like I know which direction the answer lies in,
but the path has split into even more branches.
Now I've gotten many more concerns.
- We have more concerns now.
- It's more difficult.
Since we're only in our sixth year,
I believe we still have many chances to learn and grow.
That's true.
Hee Eun! We ended up going home together.
Let's go.
Let's go back to Busan and run our business.
(The sales status of the revival match)
(1st place: Essence And Technique, 529 dollars)
(2nd place: Everything About Tteokbokki, 377 dollars)
(The largest theme park in Korea)
(An average of 14,000 visitors per day)
No one goes there just to eat.
It is better to wait in line and ride one more attraction.
I thought people in the amusement park...
would like to try something special.
Things like churros or tornado potatoes.
- Food you eat while walking around.
(Food that is convenient to carry around?)
Something both children...
and adults can enjoy.
(Food that can satisfy multiple target customers?)
How can we satisfy every target customer at the same time?
(The Third Street Arena: An amusement park)
(At 6am, an amusement park in Yongin)
We now have two teams that came back...
through the revival match.
- Who are they?
- I knew it. Who survived?
I knew this would happen.
My goodness.
- They survived!
- Tteokbokki is alive!
Everything About Tteokbokki was like a phoenix. Impressive.
As for Everything About Tteokbokki,
they've finally met the mission that's perfect for them.
Essence And Technique is a team that is remarkably good at business.
I'm back.
You guys better watch out.
Underdog revival teams often end up winning the whole thing.
This round is the 100 serving relay team match.
(Team One: Jung Ho Young and Hong Seok Cheon)
(Team Two: Edward Kwon and Kim Mi Ryeong)
(Team Three: Go Seok Hyun and Lee Sung Hoon)
(Team Four: Choi Sang Hyun and Kim Hoon)
(Team Five: Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong)
(Team Six: Kim Kwan Hoon and Kim Ho Yoon)
All six alliance teams have now been formed.
In this round,
you will operate your restaurants...
with brand-new signs and interior setups.
(Wandering Panda)
(The existing booths will be rotated 90 degrees.)
This round will be conducted as a blind test.
One member from each alliance team is allowed to leave the booth...
while wearing a full-body mascot costume.
However, you cannot speak a single word.
We will now reveal the containers you will use to sell your food.
- Containers?
- What's that?
- What?
- What are these?
- What's that?
- What? Are they containers?
How we utilize these containers...
will serve as a key strategy.
Since it’s an amusement park,
we had to think about convenience.
So what required a lot of strategic consideration...
was the container selection.
I didn't know they would make us choose containers like that.
(The first container: A soda pop container)
(The second container: A half-and-half bowl)
(The third container: A rectangular tray)
(The fourth container:)
(A cauldron-shaped bowl)
(They must choose 2 out of these 4 containers...)
(and sell 13-dollar menu items.)
(Beverage included)
(A 13-dollar combo menu)
The rectangular tray is for Japanese food.
It could be for Japanese, Korean, or even gimbap.
You could put anything in that one.
Being long wouldn't matter.
It has to be two distinct food items.
Since it’s half and half,
you can let them combine and eat them together.
Chop steak seems like a good option.
Anyway, steak has to be included.
I have no idea what we're supposed to sell in this one.
- This isn't good.
- It's too difficult.
- This is bad.
- This...
This one is quite hard to pull off.
It will be too tough to compose the menu items with that.
The teams will sell in relays using two types of containers.
(They will select two types of containers for their business.)
The starting team must complete selling out all 50 portions...
(Sold out)
before the second team can take over the business.
(The 1st dish must sell out to unlock the 2nd containers.)
Only the teams that sell out all 100 servings first,
including the 2nd team's 50 servings, will survive.
This will be fun.
All right, we can do this.
The number of restaurants to survive in this round...
is only two.
What?
My goodness. This can't be real.
(Only two alliance teams survive.)
Only two teams will survive?
In this round, if customer dissatisfaction occurs,
a penalty will be applied, adding one more serving...
from your count.
(There are 100 containers in total that need to be sold.)
(If they receive a rating of 2 stars or lower, )
(1 extra container is added.)
That means we might have to sell more than 50 servings.
So a single dish needs to deliver total satisfaction.
We will have to cook really well.
Right.
How many penalties are we going to get?
Those penalties are going to act as a crucial variable.
The amusement park opens at 10am.
Please begin preparing for operations.
(Remaining time until the opening of restaurants)
I'm confident when it comes to team battles.
I really am.
The goal is for both of us to win after all. I want to win.
The team we had in mind was...
The Sauce.
(The Sauce by Choi Sang Hyun)
I wanted to do it with someone who knows what they're doing.
The first restaurant to survive...
(1st place in Round 1, the 1,000-dollar sales race)
(A 2-to-0 victory in the 1,000-dollar sales race)
I've known Chef Sang Hyun of The Sauce...
for over ten years now.
Hoon!
If we teamed up,
I thought we would have great teamwork.
HunGry is doing very well.
I want to be there.
- Here or there?
- Yes.
Do whatever you want.
Can I pick?
The location doesn't matter.
- Right. It doesn't matter.
- We just need to do well.
It felt reassuring.
With the four of us on a team,
I thought our individual skill levels...
were top-tier, to be honest.
We met up and held about 3 or 4 meetings.
We need to choose an item with strong appeal.
Whoever sells out first wins the round.
People will come solely based on the sign.
They have no idea who is actually cooking back there.
First, we need to figure out our primary target customers.
The people coming between 12pm and 3pm...
- Right. Mostly preschool kids.
- They are mostly preschoolers.
And the moms with young kids who aren't in kindergarten.
Maybe we can name our team...
something like "Kid-Friendly."
- The team name isn't important.
- That doesn't matter.
I think it could work as part of our strategy.
I love it. I love the idea of the name and kid-friendly dishes.
- But it doesn't quite sound catchy.
- I know.
It could rather be something like "Kids' Menu."
- Kids...
- "Kids Restaurant."
- Kids Restaurant!
- Yes.
Let's go with that. Kids Restaurant.
- Kids Restaurant.
(Kids Restaurant!)
(Free cotton candy)
Aren't you too cute, Hoon?
Hurry and put it on. We all need to wear it.
- This is hilarious.
- It's cute.
We had a reason for this.
The concept of our booth was "Kids Restaurant."
I got this hat for the theme.
It's such a shame the customers won't get to see this.
- Go, Kids Restaurant!
- Go!
I don't know.
Dishes that are hard for toddlers and young kids to eat,
such as spicy food with strong flavours.
We ruled out those dishes when coming up with the menu.
So we prepared a cream pasta specifically targeted at children.
(Steak cream pasta)
The operating hours are from 12pm to 3pm,
so people will want to have lunch from 12pm.
We allocated more than...
two-third of our food budget to the first dish.
So we decided that the starting team would serve...
a cost-effective and delicious meal.
If you can get steak and pasta for 13 dollars,
who wouldn't eat here?
- I love the idea.
- I think that sounds good.
Where else could you get steak and pasta for 13 dollars?
- It's impossible.
- Right.
For the first race,
we chose the rectangular tray.
It is the container that presents the food with the most variety.
Seung Jae, did you set the water on the stove?
Yes.
- Is everything going well, Hoon?
- Yes. I have no problems.
I felt we needed a leader anyway.
We entrusted that leadership role to Chef Sang Hyun.
How long do you think this will take, Hoon?
- The blending?
- Yes.
Three more minutes.
After you do that, measure out...
- the tomato paste, Jong In.
- Okay.
Seung Jae, are you keeping an eye on the beef?
Yes.
Since I'm older, I spoke comfortably to everyone.
I organised things well and passed them along.
Seung Jae, did you hydrate the breadcrumbs?
Not yet.
You do that.
Jong In, put in the chocolate syrup.
And let's grind some cheese for the garnish.
Even without lengthy explanations, they understood well...
and knew what they had to do.
We took care of our own tasks while blending into the team.
While the ice cream is freezing,
- I'll go make cotton candy outside.
- Okay.
We brought individual timetables for all four of us.
Having a timeline set up like that...
ensures our work gets completed on schedule...
and stays on tempo.
I don't think any other team prepared as thoroughly as we did.
We're doing things that require a lot of work.
- It takes the most effort.
- Yes.
Compared to teams that were formed in a hurry,
I think our teamwork was much better.
I bet we will finish right on time. Let's do this.
(Kids Restaurant)
- Hey.
- Yes?
Do we have any chant?
- A chant?
- Chef Land, hey, hey, hey!
- Hey, hey, hey!
(Jung Ho Young and Hong Seok Cheon)
Here's my opinion.
We should sell...
the drink combo first.
- Serve that first?
- Yes.
(Hohyunghojae chose the soda pop container.)
I noticed in the table layout,
there weren't that many tables.
(600 seats in Sejong)
(400 seats in Songdo with the mat zone)
(150 seats in the amusement park)
We chose the one most suitable for the commercial zone.
People can't help but get a takeout.
That's why we chose the soda pop container.
Our strategy is to have you wear the mask in the first half,
and we'll deal with the sales first.
We expected people to grab a meal at noon.
Then people will choose something rather light later.
The first meal to serve is...
Korean rib-eye party cup grilled by the chef.
Let me quickly work on this first.
Get the meat ready.
- I'll mature it first.
- Yes, that's important.
I found high quality Korean beef, right?
I thought people in the amusement park...
would like to try something special.
So we chose Korean beef for our ingredient.
(In the morning of Round 3)
Korean beef? Rib-eye?
- Oh, Korean rib-eye?
- Korean rib-eye?
How did they meet the price range with rib-eye?
That's tough.
They're using Korean beef...
when it should be around 12 to 13 dollars?
It's impossible to meet the price.
Are they able to meet the price?
I'm curious about the rib-eye.
Tell me about the manufacturer.
(All teams are given the same ingredient cost.)
It's 570 dollars.
It costs only 270 dollars for 9kg of rib-eye?
What?
Can you get Korean beef for that price?
We'll get frozen...
- Grade 2 or 3 Korean beef.
- I see.
Yes.
We're using frozen Grade Two Korean beef.
- It'll be just over 480 dollars.
- Around 480 dollars?
Help us out.
- Try not to go...
- Over...
- over high 300 dollars.
- Okay.
Our budget is low.
It's the same menu, but made with beef?
Then I'd totally buy that too.
Korean beef was our kick.
But since we had to meet the Korean beef price,
we as chefs have the technique...
to tenderize the chewy meat.
I think this was a very good idea, Seok Cheon.
To add the stock powder.
We tenderized the meat...
by adding the stock powder and baking soda.
The veggies are pretty good for ugly veggies.
- Yes.
- With ugly veggies.
- They're not actually ugly.
They're just a bit small.
We used ugly veggies.
So we can save the ingredient cost and lower the price.
You're too smart...
for your skills.
My nickname is the fat fox.
A fat fox? Okay.
- It's 10:10am.
- Okay.
- Let's start making...
- cotton candies at 10:30am.
- Okay.
(Stir-frying ingredients endlessly)
- What time is it?
- It's 10:30am.
- Hoon.
- Yes.
Can you count the meat for me?
I lost count while counting.
Two, four, six, eight, ten.
Twenty two.
We won't be able to finish in time.
- What?
- We won't be ready in time.
What do we do?
Actually, it required a lot of ingredients.
And the sauce was too complicated.
They pan-fried Korean beef.
Then they grilled it on charcoal again.
There was so much to do that the prep time felt short.
Chef Song Hoon, is there anything else you want me to do?
Since it's a team match,
we had to cook like their menu was our own.
Here's what you need to do. Turn on high heat...
and cook only the outside.
(Jung Ho Young's french fries)
(Jung Ho Young's Korean beef skewer)
I expected them to need my help.
It's a small space,
and I knew what they were making.
We avoided using a knife as much as possible.
If we make enough in one large pot...
and make the sauce on the side,
it'll be efficient as if we're working as one team.
Chef Min Hyuk worked very hard.
He was our cheat code.
(Team Chef Land's cheat code, Park Min Hyuk)
He helped them diligently.
It was not a problem. We're a team after all.
If we get extra points for teamwork,
we'd totally make it.
Cotton candy will go crazy later.
Are they giving it out for free?
I think the cotton candy was free.
They have a good business tactic.
It'd be funny if only the two of us become popular.
Kids Restaurant has...
cotton candy.
They're serving cotton candy and ice cream.
Kids Restaurant and we had a similar theme.
They were serving cotton candy or churros.
In fact, they even had the ice cream machine ready.
But then Hoon's cotton candy...
- looks nice.
- If you shape it like that...
It depends on how they serve it.
I bet they can't do it.
There's a big difference between an owned restaurant and a rent.
I once had cotton candy in the menu...
for about three years in the past.
At first, this is what you do.
Good job.
Did you learn that from CIA?
Not from CIA.
- It looks like a UFO.
- Yes.
Our cotton candy is on another level.
It looks nice, and it has a nice colour.
Look, Hoon.
The cotton candy.
Theirs doesn't have a shape.
- No?
- Are they making it?
- It's messy.
- Really?
They only focused on serving it.
- They only focused on serving it.
- That's perfect.
I took a peek at their cotton candy.
That's not cotton candy.
That's just cotton.
I think it'd help us stand out a bit more.
It's a lot of work to make it look nice.
It's hard to make it look nice.
Gosh.
Right now,
it's 11:50am.
It's ten minutes...
- before the business opens.
- Clean it up.
Okay.
Chef Mi Ryeong is almost done.
- Yes, I'm almost done.
- Good.
Seok Cheon, let's do our chant.
- Chef Land, hey, hey, hey!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Hey!
- Let's go!
- We can do it.
(Among 6 alliance teams, )
(only two teams will survive.)
Are people coming in?
It's not as crowded as expected.
Wait. There's a line. It's crowded.
There are more than 50 people.
There are many kids.
It's the land of fantasy, Everland.
Couples.
There are families.
(The main targets are children, couples, and families.)
What if we end up leaving after eating only?
Do we have the food displayed?
- Watch your back.
- Okay.
Be careful.
- It's going to be scorching.
- True.
It's no joke.
I decided to put on the octopus mask.
(Struggling)
Welcome.
Come in.
Now, Round Three,
the 100 serving relay team match begins.
Please open your first dish.
(Choi Sang Hyun)
Let's go!
(The first dish...)
(The first dish opens.)
Let's go!
- I can't wait.
- Do you want to check it out first?
There are so many. There are 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
(The first customer)
(Passing)
Are we getting any orders yet?
- We're not getting any orders.
- They're ordering now.
(Too crowded)
That one? Spicy stir-fried pork gimbap?
(The first order is...)
(Buzz)
It's here.
(The first order goes to...)
(Kim Mi Ryeong and Edward Kwon.)
- Did we receive an order?
- Yes.
- How many orders did we get?
- Two?
Oh, just one.
Anyone who wants to join us, please come forward.
(Applicant: Kim Mi Ryeong)
- They're two strong teams.
- Yes, they're both strong.
They're two strong teams.
(Western cuisine and Korean cuisine)
I can't even imagine what they'd serve.
Destiny is calling.
I should work with Chef Edward.
I've found my love.
(The first meeting)
Chef Edward Kwon has charisma.
What's your favourite? I think this is the best.
Yes. Me too. I knew Edward Kwon was good.
My favourite Chef Edward Kwon.
(He didn't stop expressing his love for Edward Kwon.)
I'm a big fan of Chef Edward Kwon.
Working with Chef Edward Kwon...
whom I've only seen on TV.
It was something impossible to do with my idol.
I hope to do our best...
and win.
When I heard you were coming,
I prepared drinks.
You even got us a drink?
What is this? Cider?
Yes, it's Cider with the scent of yuzu.
It has the fresh yuzu flavour.
Is this part of the combo?
It's part of the combo.
(People of all ages visit the amusement park.)
(Everyone's favourite Cider will be served with the food.)
- I was thinking about gimbap.
- That's also a good idea.
- When we were young...
- Back...
- when we went on a field trip...
- Yes. Gimbap and Cider.
(Jun Seong can't take his eyes off of Edward Kwon.)
I went to the amusement park yesterday.
Yes, I heard.
There were barely any signs...
- in Korean.
- Sure it is.
(Most signs were written in English.)
Personally, I hope we don't focus too much on Korean food.
It could be western or Chinese. It could be a mix.
If the restaurant name...
sounds too Korean...
We should have that in mind.
I know it's a blind competition,
but we have...
the "Aunt" title.
So we should emphasize that title,
yet mix English...
and go with Finer Aunt's.
And for the menu...
We can write that below in Korean.
- Or...
- We don't have to...
bring out the aunt title forward.
I'm sorry, but if the sign says aunt,
even I'd expect Korean food.
I thought if we have a disagreement...
from the start,
we'd continue to have disagreements.
Then we'll go with Auntie's. But we can...
- write "The taste of your aunt..."
- The taste of your aunt...
below in Korean.
Since it's an amusement park,
and there will be a lot of children,
I thought it should be straightforward.
If we go with Auntie's,
people might get confused because of the ambiguous image.
So I think we should focus on Aunt...
- We shouldn't do that.
- We shouldn't.
(So they agreed on...)
(Aunties Kitchen)
Since it's a team match,
I thought we should avoid any noise in the beginning.
Okay. The brand name is important,
but we should compete with our food.
So we decided to go as "Aunties Kitchen."
(Edward Kwon made a concession and agreed on Aunties Kitchen.)
We went first.
(Kim Mi Ryeong's going in the first half.)
First.
We chose the half and half bowl.
Going first is like cuts both ways.
If we fail to sell everything, it'd be a game over because of us.
If we thrive, we'll get to contribute.
When we used to visit an amusement park,
we always made gimbap.
And even for field trips.
So we expected people to prefer gimbap...
and went first.
(Preparing gimbap which is a popular picnic food item)
Spicy stir-fried pork would go well with greens.
(Spicy and fragrant spring green spicy stir-fried gimbap)
And it comes with...
shrimp and chicken skewers.
You'll also get to try two types of skewers.
We're also serving children's favourite corn cheese...
with sweet potato mousse.
Since people will get to try different dishes,
it'd be popular.
I think this looks good.
(Starting with the first order...)
Spring greens... That sounds delicious.
- I'm getting one of these first.
- Okay.
(Kim Mi Ryeong and Edward Kwon)
We just got six orders.
Okay.
(Place sweet potato mousse in the container first.)
(Then place corn cheese next.)
Gosh, cheese hardened.
Wait.
This is too thick.
No. This isn't going to work. There's no other way.
Bring it here.
(To be continued)
Throw that out.
What's wrong?
It's hardened.
It's giving me stress.
(The business match begins.)
(We didn't get along.)
(It's giving me a mental breakdown.)
(I knew something went wrong.)
(Teamwork is crucial for the Round 3 mission.)
(Can't you help us with frying?)
(We didn't have good teamwork.)
(Be the first to sell 100 servings.)
(Already?)
(Are you done?)
(We're in first place.)
(We got this.)
(1 customer rating is...)
(1 customer rating is given.)
(It's not good.)
(I don't like it.)
(Their realities are like harsh business.)
Present it nicely.
(The business match becomes extreme.)
(3 penalty servings added)
(We're receiving customer ratings in real-time. It's scary.)
(Someone's getting forward...)
(when others are falling behind.)
(The result is never predictable.)
(Only 4 keys to the semifinal)
(Who will be the first to enter the semifinal?)